[Music]
Born blast cut sharp grew as spawn and
fear.
Strings rip wild as headlines appear.
Lipd circling helicopters above.
Barricades building but not enough love.
Burio sunrise. The tension begins.
Neighbors trade stories on how it got
grim.
Helicopters circling, chasing their
ghost.
Prayers for the families who need them
the most. Boots on sunset, marching
through the night.
Signs whailing and families outside.
Our games played in a time machine.
Finally see the struggle painted on
every street
[Music]
fight for the rights of liberty tonight.
They came for the neighbors with dogs
and shield lines.
Truck lights were shining as freedom
unwinds.
Commanded from towers a continent in
away.
But hope burns stubborn. It doesn't
obey.
Blue and gold is flying not turning to
gray.
Voices give louder.
Boots on sunet marching through the
night.
Silence whale and families held tight.
Power games played in the time machine.
But we see the string on every street.
[Music]
Fighting for the right.
A liberty tonight.